http://www.marshallamps.com/about/legal-information/privacy-policy

Marshall Home
About
Legal information
Privacy PolicyMarshall Amplification Plc takes your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when we collect personal information about you and how we will use your personal data.Marshall Amplification Plc registered office is Denbigh Road, Bletchley, Milton Keynes, MK1 1DQ, England, company number 00805676. We act as the ‘Data Controller’ for personal data and are registered with the UK's Information Commissioner’s Office. Our registration number is Z5713360.We will collect your personal information when you, for example:Buy or use any of our online products and or services;Subscribe to newsletters, alerts or other services from us;Contact us through various channels (in particular when you contact us via email), or ask for information about a product or service;Take part in a competition, prize draw or survey;Visit our website; orWhere you provide information publicly.  The information we collect about you Your name, address, phone and/or mobile number, your date of birth, gender and email address;Your location data. For example, a location is derived from your IP address or data such as a post code or name of a town or city;Your contact with us, such as a note or recording of a call you make, an email or letter sent, or other records of any contact with us;Your account information, account numbers or other information related to your account or included in My.Marshall;Credential information – we’ll collect passwords, hints and similar security information used for authentication and access to accounts and services;Your preferences for particular products, services and lifestyle activities when you tell us what they are, or we assume what they are, based on how you use the products and services; orSee the 'Cookies' section for details on what we collect using cookies. How we will use the information about youWe gather this information to allow us to process the setting up and administrator your online account.  We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us to develop our website and our services. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you.We will store personal information for a period not exceeding 5 years from the date when you last provided that personal information. It may be necessary to share some of your information with a third party in provision of certain services, such as forwarding a support request to a relevant national distributor or service centre. We will endeavour to share only information necessary to the specific service.You have the right to restrict the processing of your personal information by us. If you wish to do so please send an email to data.protection@marshall.com setting out details of those restrictions. We shall endeavour to comply with all such requests but there may be some limitations due to previously made public information, such as online blogs. We will however close your account and delete any information not critical to the operation of our services. MarketingWe may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please contact us in the manner set out above. Even if you do not opt out of receiving such information when you first open an online account with us or when you first indicate that you agree to the terms set out in this privacy policy you can always opt out at a later date. Use of cookies and other information-gathering technologiesCookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. We use these to make our website more efficient and to protect your information. They provide us with anonymous information to improve user experience and our content. Below is the explanation of the cookies we use and why we use them.Marshall.com cookies_ga _gta_gtag_UA_80655449_2 gid We use these cookies to collect information about how visitors use our website, to create reports and analysis. All data is collected in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited.ARRAffinity This is used by the Azure webserver, our website hosts, to try and help with routing your queries on our site.Third party cookiesYouTube cookiesWe embed videos from our official YouTube channel using YouTube’s privacy-enhanced mode.You can view YouTubes Privacy Policy here and you can view more information on embedding YouTube’s videos hereGoogle cookiesWe use Google analytics and related Google cookies to gather website statistics, and track conversion rates.You can view Google’s Privacy Policy here.Facebook cookies and pixelsWe use Facebook cookies to track activity on our website. When you subsequently use Facebook, those cookies deliver adverts that are relevant to you and your interests. The number of adverts you see will be limited by Facebook’s cookie policy for each time you visit a particular Facebook page. All Facebook cookies we use are deleted after 180 days if you do not revisit our website during that period. Read more about Facebook’s cookie policy here.Other cookiesFrom time to time we link pages out to other sites. In doing this, those sites use their cookies on our site. The relevant privacy policies are listed below:FacebookTwitterSpotifyInstagramHow can you change your cookie settings?Visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. to find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies are being used. Some control of cookies is usually allowed through the browser settings on most web browsers.Click the links below to understand how you can manage cookies on popular browsers.Google ChromeMicrosoft EdgeMozilla FirefoxMicrosoft Internet ExplorerOperaApple SafariFor any further information on other browsers, you will need to visit the browser developer’s website.Alternatively, you can opt out of Google Analytics tracking across all websites by visiting this site. How we protect your informationWe have put in place appropriate security procedures and technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal information and ensure that it is processed lawfully which includes limited access, use of passwords etc as appropriate.We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet.You have the right to contact the relevant Data Protection Authority regarding how we process your personal information. Overseas TransfersThe information you provide may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area ('EEA') that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and restrictions on its use as set out in this policy. However, if we do so, we will take steps to ensure adequate protections are in place to ensure the security of your information. The EEA comprises the EU member states plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein. By consenting to us processing your personal information this includes your consent to these transfers for the purposes specified above. Access to your information and updating and correcting your informationYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to data.protection@marshall.com. We may make a reasonable charge for this service if the request is deemed excessive, repetitive or if further copies of the same information are requested. We will endeavour to provide such information without delay and within one month of receiving a request from you to provide a copy of such information. However, we reserve the right to extend this period by a further period of up to two months if the request for information is deemed to be complex. In such a case we will inform you within one month of the request that we intend to extend the period of time to provide the information along with our reasoning.We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to Marshall Amplification Plc changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details, or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by contacting us at the above address. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate. Sale of businessIf our business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business. Your consentBy agreeing to the terms and conditions required to open a MyMarshall Account, or by otherwise choosing an option, when offered, to agree to any of our other terms and conditions, you have consented to the use of your personal information in the manner set out in this policy. You may withdraw your consent at any time by sending an email to data.protection@marshall.com requesting that we erase all or any part of any personal information we hold about you. We shall comply so long as the information is not critical to the operation of our services, or where we are required by law to maintain the information. Changes to Privacy PolicyWe keep our Privacy Policy under regular review. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page, and place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 8 October 2019. How to contact usWe welcome your views about our website and our Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please contact Marshall Amplification Plc, at the above address. Links to other websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to this website so when you access links to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
Where next?
Marshall Amps
Eden Amps
Natal Drums
Lifestyle
Marshall Records
This site uses cookies to improve your experience. By continuing we assume that you're ok for us to store cookies on your device.You can change your cookie settings at any time, or delete cookies, by going to your browser settings.
Accept Cookies
